spinrewriter.com 2019-04-29

# SmileyTech Solutions - Privacy Policy

The » _Privacy Policy_ « published on this page applies to all websites and services that are represented by the SmileyTech Solutions (unregistered) trademark. This includes the following services and their websites: Smiley SEO, Spin Rewriter, Spin Distribute, Site Guardian Pro, Pro Article Writing, Rankings Done Right, SmileyTech Solutions (this website). 

Our privacy policy is written to be GDPR compliant and also explains how we process and collect personal data of our users (both customers and visitors). 

### 1\. Privacy Policy

The privacy of our users is of utmost importance to us. Accordingly, we have developed this » _Privacy Policy_ « in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy: 

**»** Before or at the time of collecting personal information, where appropriate, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 

**»** We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 

**»** We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 

**»** Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 

**»** We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 

**»** We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. 

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit this website, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

### 2\. Personal Data Collected

Email Address  
**Customers:** Email address is collected for login purposes, for delivery of required system emails (forgotten password reset, issues with an account), for delivery of emails about latest software updates and promotion purposes, and for communication with our support desk (with the intention of resolving any issues encountered). Email address is collected and processed on the basis of performance of contract and legitimate interest. 

**Visitors (optional):** If you so choose, we collect your email address for delivery of emails about our company, our latest software updates, and promotion purposes. Email address is collected and processed on the basis of consent. 

IP Address  
**Customers:** IP address is logged for login and security purposes. Collected and processed on the basis of legitimate interest. 

**Visitors:** IP address is logged for differentiation of visitors to our website and personalization of content based on the presumed country of the IP address. It's also logged for security purposes. Collected and processed on the basis of legitimate interest. 

Full Name  
**Customers:** Full name is collected for the purposes of email and other communication, with the intention of performance of our services. Collected and processed on the basis of performance of contract. 

**Visitors (optional):** If you contact us, we use your name for the purposes of communication. Collected and processed on the basis of consent. IP address is logged for differentiation of visitors to our website and personalization of content based on the presumed country of the IP address. It's also logged for security purposes. Collected and processed on the basis of legitimate interest. 

We keep personal identifiable data for anti-fraud reasons for up to one year.

### 3\. External Vendors Used

Personal data collected is shared with external services we use for purposes stated below. 

**1) Google Analytics (Google Inc.)** \- Analytics that let us track the behaviour of visitors on our website. This helps us understand where visitors are coming, which pages on our website they're visiting, and in what way they are navigating our website. This in turn lets us determine if there are any bottlenecks in terms of confusing user interface elements, and resolving these issues lets us provide a better user experience. Based on this analytics data we can then improve our content and personalize the experience of individual users. Privacy Shield certified. 

### 4\. Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

### 5\. Cookies

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit any of our websites. This could include only showing you a pop-up once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as registered-members-only areas and forums. 

We might also use third party advertisements to support some of our websites. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our websites as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into your account. 

### 6\. User Rights

Every user of our services is entitled to: 

**»** the right of access (which means the right to know whether data concerning him or her are being processed and if so, to access this data), 

**»** the right to rectification (when user's personal data is inaccurate, we will correct the information in question), 

**»** the right to erasure (when user withdraws consent or services are terminated, we will erase user's personal data, subject to specified retention periods), 

**»** the right to data portability (upon user's request, we will provide personal data concerning him or her in a structured, commonly-used and machine-readable format). 

### 7\. Retention Period

We delete our users' personal data after one year of consent withdrawal or termination of contract. 

### 8\. Automated Decision Making (Profiling)

For the purpose of providing a better service, we do user profiling on the basis of our legitimate business interests. Examples include automated subscription-renewal reminders when a user is close to the expiration date of his or her current subscription, reminders to do a specific activity to continue a process, and other similar activities. The consequences of profiling are limited to notifications to the user. 

### 9\. Internal Processes

Our staff has restricted access to personal identifiable information unless required by the law or lawful processing of personal data. We have an internal policy and procedures in place to handle potential data breaches. We also have procedures and policies in place to comply with data portability and our users' right to be forgotten. 

### 10\. Marketing and Remarketing

We may promote our services through remarketing. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with any of our websites. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show ads for our services on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on user's prior visits to any of our websites. 

To opt out of customized Google Display Network ads, [click here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjO-P9kncoNV8waYtavL8ZEwWRLAhhGX7ESyhREjNPEH7nMGxWksJO-uFQYNVKIjB9_qnXgHCHNy2WETTCMIXVQ9R_Oea0MHA_VGyn22H4gZ6ZzDwhG6WUzEyMYFOOFEsH-XUeLEPx9qaWYBbMCH9J2Pi6g9yczOd4TKR-Hncu30k0iavWl68hNVXe0XNEKqTFn_x-A5x6uNuRE2_f9MSeEWE5UApqYhSa8fAPM5tGWnjrOwc6bnYApRXRe1_HQ0HP0H4qK&hl=en "Google - Ads Preferences Manager"). To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects, please visit <https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

Any information collected this way is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by us or our partners for any other purpose. 

### 11\. Email Marketing Policy

By creating a registered account on any of the websites that are represented by the (unregistered) SmileyTech Solutions trademark, you are also agreeing that we can send you email messages pertaining to our services. 

You can always unsubscribe from receiving our email messages by clicking a link in the footer of our email messages, or responding with the word 'Unsubscribe'. 

All email communication from us will be relevant to your interests and will comply with CAN-SPAM act. 

We maintain a ZERO tolerance policy towards the sending of spam email. Spam email is defined as Unsolicited Commercial Email (UCE). 

We also require our affiliate partners and advertising partners to comply with our own Marketing Policy. In the event that our affiliate partners send spam email to users without their permission, they risk immediate cancellation of their account. We neither condone nor tolerate the sending of unsolicited or spam email. 

If you have any questions in relation to our Privacy Policy, or you would like to send a data portability request, or you would like to send a right-to-be-forgotten request, please contact us at the email address below. 

The following registered business is recognized as the SmileyTech Solutions trademark holder: 

**INFINET d.o.o.** (officially translated: INFINET LLC)  
Kunaverjeva ulica 9  
1000 Ljubljana  
Slovenia, EUROPE

VAT ID Number: SI-97705446  
   ( _this business is registered for VAT purposes_ )

Registration Number: 3914828000  
   ( _Agency of the Republic of Slovenia for Public Legal Records and Related Services - AJPES_ )

Contact Email Address: _available in the footer of all pages of this website_

**Most Recent Revision:** This document has been updated on December 4th, 2018 at 8:21 AM EST (New York time).
